伯纳黛特  伴娘的礼服找得怎样了
So, Bernadette, how goes the hunt for bridesmaid dresses?
如果你不介意看上去像个
Well, if you don't mind looking like
橙色交通锥的话  已经找到了
an orange traffic cone, great.
闺蜜们  我有办法解决礼服的问题
Girlfriends, I have the answer to our dress problems.
真的吗
Really?
十二年前  我表妹艾琳全家
12 years ago, my cousin Irene and her entire family
在她结婚前晚  全死于一场可怕的
died in a horrific carbon monoxide accident
一氧化碳中毒事故
the night before her wedding.
人间惨剧啊
That's horrible.
这倒未必
Yes and no.
那些还没被穿过的伴娘衣服
All those bridesmaids dresses remain unused
咱们就能免费享用了
and available to us for free.
只能说  大难全死
So it seems that cloud of odorless deadly gas
必有后福啊
had a silver lining after all.
你们看
Check it out,
都还在袋子里呢
still in the bags.
不是说尸袋  是说礼服防尘袋
The gowns, not the bridesmaids.
这个嘛
I don't know.
穿死人剩的衣服不太好吧
Dead people's dresses?
是啊  而且那超短袖...
Yeah, and cap sleeve...
我还希望你们不会注意到呢
Oh, I was hoping you wouldn't notice.
艾琳总对打折的服饰毫无抵抗力
Irene was always a slave to a good bargain when it came to clothes,
超短袖太冷  开暖气才一氧化碳中毒的
and sadly as it turned out, space heaters.
女士们  自制啊
Ladies, please.
这间屋子曾是一个智慧的集合地
These four walls once housed an intellectual salon
在这里  大脑和胃袋都能吸收到营养
where the mind received nourishment as well as the stomach.
虽然没人有错
But through no one's fault,
佩妮
Penny,
但晚餐谈话的质量的确下滑了
the quality of dinner conversation in this apartment has declined.
再次重申  这事谁都不怪
And again, I'm looking at no one in particular,
佩妮
Penny.
好吧
Fine.
那你想聊什么  谢尔顿
What would you like to talk about, Sheldon?
你居然问谢尔顿想聊什么
你何苦要逼死大家呢
Why do you hate us?
我准备了一些应该能同时吸引
I've prepared a number of topics that should appeal to
高阶谈天霸  与低档聊天人的话题
both the advanced and novice conversationalists.
你明显意有所指的瞄了我
Okay, that time you looked at me.
谁不想瞄你啊
Who didn't?
你的皮肤白璧无瑕
Your skin is like alabaster.
感觉根本没毛孔啊
Do you even have pores?
第一个话题
Topic one:
欧洲核子研究中心宣布超光速离子的存在
"Faster-than-light particles at CERN--
这是范式转换的新发现
paradigm-shifting discovery
还是像它们的乳酪一样千疮百孔的笑谈
or another Swiss export as full of holes as their cheese?"
开始高谈阔论吧
And converse.
好吧  谁想来
All right, who wants to go
我屋子里看看婚礼杂志
to my apartment and look at bridal magazines?
我去看
Oh, me.
完全不怪任何人  谢尔顿  我们闪人了
Through no one's fault, Sheldon, we're leaving.
等等人家啦
Wait for moi.
你也要走吗
You're leaving?
谢尔顿  有时你忘记了我也是一名女士
Sheldon, sometimes you forget, I'm a lady.
女人天生带一种雌激素  促使我们一边
and with that, comes with an oestrogen fuel need to page through
翻阅光鲜厚重的杂志  一边暗恨自己身材不佳
thick glossy magazines that make me hate my body.
新话题:  女人们
New topice: women.
讨人喜爱的谜女还是令人厌恶的八婆
Delightfully mysterious or bat-crap crazy?
说得好
Totally.
超短袖有哪里不好了
What's wrong with cap sleeves?
只要身形适合  穿起来超卡哇伊啊
If you have the right figure for it, they're adorable.
《生活大爆炸》
第五季第八集
哟  艾米  什么风把你吹来这了
Hey, Amy, what brings you to our neck of the woods?
你们神经科学部门借了我朊病毒培养箱
Your neurology department loaned me a culture of prions
来协助我牛海绵状脑病的研究
for my research on bovine spongiform encephalopathy.
她是来讨一杯疯牛病
She popped by to borrow a cup of mad cow disease.
把脑部退化疾病说得诙谐可不容易
It's hard to make degenerative brain maladies hilarious,
但你总能化正经为笑料
and yet somehow you do it.
餐桌上谈这个还"真"有意思啊
That's fun to have in a lunchroom.
真正的乐趣始于你能挑选
The real fun starts when you get to pick the rat
任意小白鼠来注入病毒
you're going to feed it to, and maybe you choose
搞不好选中的就是那只老咬你的鼠妈妈
the beady-eyed little mother who's been biting you all week.
拜托  我们在吃饭呢
Please, we're eating.
可不可以把那东西拿下桌
Can we get that off the table
然后换个话题聊啊
and change the subject?
换话题吗
Can we?
屏息以待吧
Stand back...
看哥怎么将聊天打屁升华到指点江山
while I turn this conversation into a "Conver-sensation."
这次完全是你自找的
This time, it's your fault.
我有一百个按字母顺序排列的话题  从
I have 100 alphabetized topics from
"洋蓟:这不过是蓟长得大一点罢了"
"Artichoke-- come on, people, it's just a giant thistle,"
到"《打鼾》:以鼾声为诗"
to "Zzz-- the onamona-poetry of sleep."
艾米  疯牛病毒得多久才弄得死我啊
Amy, how long would it take for that mad cow disease to kill me?
我也不知道  四五年吧
I don't know, four or five years.
不行  远水救不了近火
No, it's not gonna do it.
伯纳黛特一直发给我
Oy. Bernadette keeps texting me pictures
佩妮试伴娘礼服的照片
of Penny in bridesmaid dresses.
她们现在在逛街吗
They're out shopping right now?
是啊
Yeah.
只有她们两人吗
Just the two of them?
我想是吧
I guess.
很好  非常好
That's cool, that's cool.
她们为毛问我这种事情啊
Why are they asking me about this stuff?
哪个男人能知道鸡心领是什么玩意
What guy knows what a sweetheart neckline is?
莱纳德要终点前冲刺啦
Leonard's coming down the home stretch!
加油啊  马儿  你能行的
Come on, horsey, you can do this!
该死  拜托  大腿肌肉  你也能行
Damn. Come on, thigh muscles, you can do this!
太棒了  冠军
Yes! First place.
我肯定能当一名好骑士  要不是小时候太高...
I would have been a great jockey if I weren't too tall.
和害怕马的话
and scared of horses.
谢尔顿  该你了
Sheldon, you're up.
什么
What?
快点  该你了
Come on, it's your turn.
我们说好要呼吸新鲜空气的
We said we'd get more fresh air.
抱歉  我有点心烦意乱
Sorry. I'm a little distracted.
我联系不到艾米了
I can't seem to get in touch with Amy.
不管是发邮件  邀请视频
I tried e-mail, video chat,
在推特上找她  或在她主页上留言
tweeting her, posting on her Facebook wall,
发短信  都没用
texting her, nothing.
你打过她家里电话吗
Did you try calling her on the telephone?
对呀  打座机
The telephone.
莱纳德  在你的简单世界里
You know, Leonard, in your own simple way,
你是个举世无双的天才
you may be the wisest of us all.
语音信箱
Voice mail.
真是奇了怪了
Curiouser and curiouser.
要是你不放心  我们可以过去
If you're worried, we can go over there
看看她是否有事
and see if she's all right.
好吧
Okay.
话说我看到一条新闻
You know, I heard in the news
她家那一带有人目击山猫出没
a bobcat has been spotted in her neighborhood.
艾米很安全  不会被山猫吃掉的
I don't think Amy was eaten by a bobcat.
谁说艾米被山猫吃掉了
Who thinks Amy was eaten by a bobcat?
你呀
You do?
莱纳德  我不过是说说当地新闻
Leonard, I was just mentioning an interesting local news item.
都怪你  害我开始担心艾米被山猫吃掉了
Now, thanks to you, I'm worried Amy's been eaten by a bobcat.
就忘了山猫这档事吧
Forget about the bobcat.
你猛提山猫  谁忘得掉啊
How can I? You won't stop talking about it!
*世间伤心事*
*Everybody hurts*
*时有心伤*
*Sometimes*
*惟见泪千行*
*Everybody cries*
*世间伤心事*
*Everybody hurts*
*时有心伤*
*Sometimes.*
她哭哭啼啼的
She sounds weepy.
我讨厌人家哭哭啼啼  咱们走吧
I don't like weepy. Let's go.
她可是你朋友
She's your friend.
爷们点
Step up.
艾米  艾米  艾米
Amy. Amy. Amy.
撤了
Bye.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
爷我是单身  不用搅和这破事
I'm single, I don't need this crap.
谢尔顿  你来做什么
Sheldon, what are you doing here?
我和你的电子通信
You didn't respond to
你全都没回应
any of my electronic communications.
我想一个人待着
I wanted to be alone.
你想聊聊吗
Would you like to talk about it?
友情提醒  想回答"不想说"可别客气
And keep in mind that "No" is a perfectly viable answer.
谢尔顿  我的世界要崩溃了
Sheldon, my world is crumbling around me.
按照程序
Point of order.
因为你不开心  按照惯例
As you're in distress, it would be customary
我该给你倒杯热饮
for me to offer you a hot beverage.
但我是你的客人
But I'm a guest in your home,
按照惯例  你该给我倒杯饮料
so it would be customary for you to offer me a beverage.
你想要怎么来面对面互倒饮料呀
How do you want to proceed vis-à-vis beverages?
无所谓
It doesn't matter.
都无所谓了
Nothing matters.
如果你想聊别的  不谈这事
If you'd like to take your mind off what's troubling you,
坊间传言  有人目击这附近有山猫出没
uh, word on the street is a bobcat has been spotted.
佩妮和伯纳黛特没叫我
Penny and Bernadette went shopping
就自己去买伴娘礼服了
for bridesmaids dresses without me.
这让你...
And that made you feel...
不开心吗
sad?
是的
Yes.
我就知道
I knew it.
继续说
Just keep going.
我好像还挺会读心啊
I guess I'm good at this.
我以为她们是喜欢和我一起玩的
It's just, I thought they liked hanging out with me,
原来我只是自己骗自己
but I guess I was fooling myself.
是不是她们来你家的时候
When they were over here,
你没给人家倒饮料啊
did you fail to offer them a beverage?
某些人对这事很在意很不爽
'Cause I can see how that could stick in someone's craw.
谢尔顿  我想请你做件事
Sheldon, I'm going to ask you something,
希望你不要用异样眼光看待
and I'd like you to keep an open mind.
一贯如此
Always.
此时此刻  我很渴望
At this moment, I find myself
与人有亲密行为和肢体接触
craving human intimacy and physical contact.
亲娘咧
Oh, boy.
你知道我们的关系仅限于精神层面
You know ours is a relationship of the mind.
我提议
Proposal.
咱俩一夜激情  大战数千回合
One wild night of torrid lovemaking
既能抚慰我心  也令我胯下湿热
that soothes my soul and inflames my loins.
反提议
Counterproposal.
我会轻轻地梳你的头
I will gently stroke your head
然后反复地说  "谁是乖乖艾米宝贝啊"
and repeat, "aw, who's a good Amy""
那这样如何
How about this?
法式热吻  七分钟的巅峰体验
French kissing-- seven minutes in heaven
在你上我二垒后划下句点
culminating in second base.
我帮你揉脖子
Neck massage...
然后你给我倒杯饮料
...then you get me that beverage.
我们抱一下  不商量了
We cuddle. Final offer.
好吧
Very well.
真要命
Oh, boy.
我就说说  二垒你触手可得...
I'm just saying, second base is right there.
我在考虑给自己搞个另类造型
Mm, I'm thinking about adopting some quirky affectation,
比如弄个烟斗  单片眼镜
like a pipe or a monocle
或是翘八字胡
or a handlebar mustache.
给外面那些满脑子想钓
For all those girls out there
印度钻石王老五一个明确的目标吗
looking for the Indian Monopoly man?
这国家太危险了
This is not a safe place.
什么东西都不能露白
You can't share anything here.
你们两个  给哥管好你们的女人
The two of you need to get your women in line!
啥
What?
昨一整晚  我被强迫
Last night I was strong-armed
听那烦人的竖琴
into an evening of harp music
还得让情绪化的艾米·法拉·福勒熊抱
and spooning with an emotional Amy Farrah Fowler.
本来那天晚上
This on a night
我是计划好要解决
that I had originally designated for solving
更高自旋引力场下的时空几何问题
the space-time geometry in higher-spin gravity
以及搭乐高死星的呢
and building my Lego Death Star.
结果因为你们的马子  佩妮和伯纳黛特
And why? Your gal pals, Penny and Bernadette,
偷偷跑去买婚礼垃圾  也不叫上艾米
went out shopping for some wedding nonsense without Amy,
她们完全没有想过
an action they took with no thought or regard
她们会影响到我  影响弦理论的未来
as to how it would affect me, the future of string theory
还影响我的乐高欢乐时光
or my Lego fun time!
那你想我们怎么办呢
What do you want us to do about it?
你显然没仔细听我的主题句
You clearly weren't listening to my topic sentence:
管好你们的女人
Get your women in line!
叫她们去跟艾米道歉  把关系修复好
You make them apologize to Amy and set things right.
我是个搞科研的人  不是某人的抱抱兔
I am a man of science, not someone's snuggle bunny!
为什么要我去跟佩妮谈
Why do I have to talk to Penny?
她又不是我女朋友
She's not my girlfriend.
四年前是你请她过来吃午饭的
You invited her to lunch four years ago.
她的事全怪你  你给我搞定她
Everything about her is on you; you make it so!
-木须肉是佩妮的  -谢谢
- Moo-shu is Penny. - Thank you.
谢尔顿呢
Where's Sheldon?
他昨晚熬夜了
He was up late last night,
我提早喂他食  哄他睡觉了
so I gave him an early dinner and put him to bed.
你真是体贴
That's so sweet.
不过明天一大早  他就会起床闹着玩了
Yeah, but now he's gonna be up at dawn and want to play.
其实呢
So, listen, guys,
他昨晚之所以熬夜是因为
the reason he was up late is because he was
他要照顾艾米
taking care of Amy.
她有点伤心
She's kind of upset.
为什么
Why?
她的感情有点受伤  因为你们
Her feelings got hurt because you guys
没叫她一起去逛街
went dress shopping without her.
我跟你说了她会不高兴
I told you that would happen.
这是她第一次做伴娘
Okay, look, this is her first time being a bridesmaid
她有点兴奋过头了
and she's just getting a little crazy with it.
她老是不停地说不同文化里的伴娘习俗
She keeps on telling us stories about bridesmaid traditions
而且都是得脱得光溜溜
in other cultures, and they're all about
互相给对方搓澡的那种
getting naked and washing each other.
对  她还老想知道
Yeah, and she keeps trying
我们的月经有没有同步
to figure out if our cycles have synced up
我们才能自诩为"三个同经手"
so we can call ourselves "The three menstra-teers"
我们以为不叫她
We thought it would be easier
一起去逛礼服会比较省事
to look at dresses one time without her.
我感觉好内疚
I feel terrible.
我也内疚  我们会找她谈
I know. Me, too. We'll talk to her.
等等
Hey, wait,
她怎么知道的
how did she find out?
拉杰告的密
Raj did it.
他说下次还会揭你们的短
And he says he would do it again.
好吧  对不起
Hey, I'm sorry.
你给我发照片  我当时没多想就说漏嘴了
You sent me the picture; I wasn't thinking.
-华仔  -别这样  平时
- Oh, Howie. - Well, hey, I'm usually
我的嘴巴还是挺严的
pretty good at not blabbing.
你跟我说了那么多他们的事
You tell me tons of stuff about these guys,
我从来都没说出去
and I never repeat it.
-你跟他说什么了  -没说啥
- What do you tell him? - Oh,
就一些枕边的私房话
you know, just pillow talk.
你们什么都不用担心
You guys have nothing to worry about.
咱两相好时  你没跟人家说啥吧
Hold on, did you talk about us when we were dating?
没有  你的小秘密我都没说过
No. All your little secrets are fine.
是啊  她绝对没说
Yes, absolutely fine.
我迟些再告诉你
I'll tell you later.
来吧  肿瘤
Come on, tumor.
来吧  肿瘤  老娘要的就是扩散的小恶性胶质瘤
Come on, tumor, Mama needs an aggressive little glioblastoma.
爽啊  脑瘤
Yay, brain tumor!
你得知有脑瘤时的反映估计跟我不一样
Probably not the same reaction you had when you got the news.
-嗨  -你好
- Hi. - Hello.
你们怎么来了
What are you doing here?
我们是来道歉的
Well, look, we just wanted to apologize
那天没叫上你一起去逛礼服
for not bringing you with us the other day.
没必要道歉  这就跟《芝麻街》里说的一样
That's not necessary-- it's like Sesame Street says:
"这个东西跟与众不同"
"One of these things is not like the other,
"这个东西将孤独终老"
one of these things should die alone."
别这样嘛  艾米  让我们补偿你
Come on, Amy, let us make it up to you.
咱们办个闺蜜之夜
We'll have a girl's night;
你想干啥咱就干啥
we'll do whatever you want.
我们可以去韩国洗浴中心
We can go down to the Korean baths
照你说的那样
and do that thing you were talking about
互相给对方搓澡
where we wash each other.
戴着丝瓜络手套搓  不是用手摸
With-with loofah mitts, no hands.
没关系  我很高兴发生这样的事
It's okay. I'm glad this happened.
我再也不用假装某个美女
I can stop pretending that some beautiful girl
和她找准角度还算可爱的朋友
and her cute-in-the-right-light friend
喜欢和我一起玩了
want to hang out with me.
艾米  我们真的很抱歉
Amy, we're really sorry.
对  我们觉得特内疚
Yeah, we feel awful.
别  我会没事的  你们也不是第一个
Don't. I'll be okay. You're not the first girls
我以为是我的朋友  结果处处躲着我的女孩子
I thought were friends with me who ended up shunning me.
感觉就像回到了小学  初中
It's like elementary school, junior high,
高中  大学  研究院
high school, undergrad, grad school,
还有去挪威交换的那学期一样
and that semester abroad in Norway all over again.
别这样嘛  艾米
Oh, come on, Amy.
你不懂
You don't get it.
看看这个大脑
Look at this brain.
我实在不想看
I don't really want to.
这就像我们
This is us.
伯纳黛特  你就是善于
Bernadette, you are the analytical,
科学分析的左脑
scientific left hemisphere.
佩妮  你就是有自主创造力的右脑
Penny, you're the creative, spontaneous right hemisphere.
艾米在哪呢
And where's Amy?
她在这里  可怜的小肿瘤
She's right here-- the sad little tumor
没人愿意跟她一起去逛街
no one wants to go dress shopping with.
艾米  你不是肿瘤
Amy, you're not a tumor.
佩妮  告诉她她不是肿瘤
Penny, tell her she's not a tumor.
你知道亚历山大·格拉汉姆·贝尔
Did you know that when Alexander Graham Bell
发明电话时
invented the telephone,
他提议接电话时说"啊嘿"吗
he proposed answering it with "Ahoy"?
啊嘿
Ahoy.
我喜欢
I like it.
艾米  是你吗
Amy? Is that you?
你喝酒啦
Have you been drinking?
你说什么  没我屁屁个错...
I'm sorry, I bet my sweet what?
好吧  我们这就去
Well, all right. We're on our way.
怎么了
What's going on?
艾米在一家贩酒店的停车场喝得烂醉
It would seem Amy is drunk in a liquor store parking lot.
真的吗  艾米
Really? Amy?
莱纳德  你该庆幸自己留不住女人
Leonard, be glad you can't keep a woman.
她们真是难搞
They are a handful.
看哪
Oh, look.
是小谢和小莱驾到
It's Sheldon and little Leonard.
嗨  小莱
Hi, little Leonard.
嗨  艾米
Hi, Amy.
嗨  小"抱"贝
Hey, Cuddles.
小"抱"贝
Cuddles?
对  小"抱"贝  我们抱过了
Yes, Cuddles. We cuddled.
少幼稚的猛问了  莱纳德
Grow up, Leonard.
艾米  你在这干嘛
Amy, what are you doing here?
我来这买酒
I came here to get a bottle of wine
佩妮教过我  借酒浇愁
like Penny taught me to do when you're sad.
是啊  但你怎么不回家喝
Yeah, but why didn't you go back to your apartment?
你没上过中学吗  莱纳德
Didn't you go to high school, Leonard?
酷小孩都在停车场鬼混
Parking lots are where all the cool kids hang out.
虽然那些王八蛋从没邀请过我来
Not that the rat bastards ever invited me.
我们还是带你回家吧
Maybe we should get you home.
等等  等等  谢尔顿
Oh, hang on, hang on, hang on. Sheldon,
要怎么样你才肯去隔壁
what would it take for you to go into that liquor store,
买一瓶烈酒
buy a bottle of hooch,
然后带我去街对面那家旅馆
take me across the street to that motel,
跟我大搞特搞一番呢
and have your way with me?
是啊  谢尔顿  你要怎样才肯
Yeah, Sheldon, what would it take?
我求求你们了  快走吧
I'm begging both of you, please, let's go.
好吧
Okay.
来吧
Come on.
起来没事啦
Upsy-daisy.
终于有人碰我二垒了
Ooh, finally someone found second base.
我懂你的痛
I know how you feel.
我的大脑前庭也像被刀子划过一样
I got a knife slicing through my frontal lobe, too.
找我干嘛
What do you want?
是要我把友谊手镯还给你吗
Do you want me to give the friendship bracelet back?
我没给过你友谊手镯
I never gave you a friendship bracelet.
我们刚认识时我做了一个  假装是你给我的
When we first met, I made one and pretended you gave it to me.
你要的话  我可以还给你
You can have it back if you want.
不  你给自己做的  我想你好好留着
No, you made that for you; I want you to have it.
我们知道你很伤心  你完全有理由伤心
We know you're upset, and you have every right to be,
如果可以  请再给我们一个机会
but if it's okay with you, we'd like a second chance
纠正我们的错误
to make things right.
我们真的很抱歉
We are really sorry,
我们想努力向你表达
and we were trying to think of some way to show you
我们有多在乎你
how much we care about you.
所以
Which is why
如果你能当我婚礼的首席伴娘
it would mean so much if you would agree
那就真是太好了
to be the maid of honor at my wedding.
什么  等等  这是什么恶作剧吗
What? Wait, is this some kind of practical joke?
就像在挪威  我所谓的"朋友"
Like in Norway, when my "Friends"
骗我跟发情的水獭洗桑拿那样吗
trapped me in a sauna with a horny otter?
不  我真的想请你当我的首席伴娘
No. I-I want you to be the maid of honor.
我的天哪
Oh, my gosh.
都没有人请我当过首席伴娘呢
No one's every asked me to be the maid of honor before.
哦  不对
Well, that's not true.
有过一次  不过她们都死了
Once, but then they all died.
这么说你答应啦
So is that a yes?
答应  当然答应
Yes. Yes.
老天哪
Oh, my gosh,
我有太多事要做了
I-I have so much to do.
要准备新娘婚前派对和单身女郎派对
There's the bridal shower and the bachelorette party.
单身女郎派对要做什么好呢
What should we do for the bachelorette party?
我知道了  我们去印第安人的蒸汗屋
Oh, I know-- we'll go to a Native American sweat lodge,
带上龙舌兰酒  去烂泥里打滚
we'll take peyote, roll around in the mud,
接着在伯纳黛特裸体上画生育符号
and paint fertility symbols on Bernadette's naked body.
终于要去做这事了
So that's happening.
是啊  当然  真好
Yeah, sure, sure.
拉斯维加斯也很好玩啊
Vegas is fun, too.
我有种想哭的冲动
I feel like crying.
当然  可能只是荷尔蒙作祟
Of course, I could just be hormonal.
等等  说不定我们的月经终于同步了
Oh, wait. Maybe our menses are finally syncing up.
伯纳黛特你快到了吗
Bernadette?
没有吗  佩妮呢
No? Penny?
-抱歉  -真的吗
- Sorry. - Really?
好啦  是到了
Okay, yeah.
太好了
Yay!
首席伴娘艾米·菲拉·福勒的
Maid of honor Amy Farrah Fowler's
婚礼录像之"精彩幕后故事"
amazing behind-the-scenes wedding video,
片段一
take one.
我们只是在试衣服
We're just trying on dresses--
真的要拍吗
do we really need to record this?
抱歉  你是首席伴娘吗
I'm sorry, are you the maid of honor?
我是新娘
I am the bride.
所以你不是  开拍
So no. And action.
觉得怎样
What do you think?
我喜欢
I love it!
这身什么啊  尼姑装吗
What are you, a nun?
拜托  闺蜜  露点肉肉嘛
Come on, bestie, let's see some skin.
艾米  真性感
Amy! Looking sexy!
你以为这里没镜子的吗
You think they don't have mirrors in there?
我当然知道自己有多美
I know how I look.
伯纳黛特  你真是太美了
Bernadette, you look beautiful!
-是很美  -谢谢
- You do. - Thank you.
没佩妮那么美  不过还是挺美
Not Penny beautiful, but beautiful.
快点  闺蜜  到你了
Come on, bestie, you're up.
再等我一会儿
Give me a minute.
你在干嘛啊  这么慢
What is taking you so long?
艾米  滚出去
Oh, Amy! Get the hell out of here!
-抱歉  抱歉  -天哪
- Sorry, sorry. - Oh, God.
-艾米  -抱歉
- Amy! - Sorry.